export const data = [
    {
      question: "What singular quality, one might ask, distinguishes the moonflower from the common multitude of blooms?",
      option1: "They unfold their blossoms solely in the winter season",
      option2: "They reserve their blooming for the hours of night",
      option3: "They assume a different hue upon the rising of the sun",
      option4: "They are found to flourish only in the vicinity of waters",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "The moment I first laid eyes upon you, I beheld a princess wandering a moonlit garden. What tender name did I bestow upon you then?",
      option1: "My Night Blossom",
      option2: "My Princess",
      option3: "My Moonflower",
      option4: "Chockie",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "In this quartet of my most earnest apologies, I beseech thee, upon which part do we presently find ourselves?",
      option1: "Turning the Soil",
      option2: "The Seeds of Sorrow",
      option3: "Moon in Full Glory Over the Nocturnal Garden",
      option4: "The Final Petition of Mine Heart",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "I beseech thee, which love composition is held most dear by my soul at thy moment?",
      option1: "Angel numbers - Chris Brown",
      option2: "Count me out - Kendrick Lamar",
      option3: "I Wanna be yours - Dramatic Violin",
      option4: "Luminary - Joel Sunny",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Dost thou recall the moment when tears of gratitude did grace thine eyes, upon receiving that which thy heart had long desired?",
      option1: "At our first meeting of eyes",
      option2: "At that initial moment when I did declare unto thee my love in reply",
      option3: "When I bought you your favorite cake for your birthday",
      option4: "You visited me for the first time at my student residence",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Among these most delectable cakes presented before thee, choose wisely, for it shall be the only confection thou art to partake of for the remainder of thy days.",
      option1: "Black Forest",
      option2: "Red Velvet",
      option3: "Chocolate Truffle",
      option4: "Vanilla ",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Among these gentle flowers, one alone must be selected to mirror thy spirit for all thy days",
      option1: "Moonflower",
      option2: "Red Rose",
      option3: "Blue Violet",
      option4: "Sunflower",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Should the crown be placed upon thy brow, by what name wouldst thou be addressed within thy kingdom?",
      option1: "Nella B",
      option2: "Princess of the Moonlit Garden",
      option3: "Empress of the Night",
      option4: "Princess Chanell",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Tell me, Your Grace, what dost thou value above all else in matters of love and devotion?",
      option1: "Loyalty",
      option2: "Kindness",
      option3: "Money",
      option4: "To feel safe and secure in the arms of the one you love",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of thy qualities hath most captivated my admiration?",
      option1: "Your Smile",
      option2: "Your Eyes",
      option3: "Your Voice",
      option4: "Your buttocks",
      ans: 2,
    },
  ];